

Lal Bdr. Budhachhetri

WEB DESIGNER

CONTACT

P 9865818795

E lalbahadurbc2054@gmail.com

W https://lalbahadurbc.com.np

G https://github.com/stu9437l

EDUCATION

Dhangadhi Engineering College 2016-2021

Dhangadhi, Kailali Bachelor of Computer science and technologgy

NAST 2014-2016

Dhangadhi, Kailali Higher Secondary Education Board

SUMMARY

Enthusiastic front-end developer focused on crafting great web experiences. Designing and coding have been my passion since the day I started working with computers but I found myself as Web Developer since 2021.

And Passionate about continuous learning from the seniors while still nurturing junior developers. I am still seeking a desired and challenging position in your company.

EXPERIENCE

Web Developer

Neputertech Pvt. Ltd. (2021 - current)

- Proficient in developing and managing web applications in any company.
- Overcame the initial complexity of web development through research, self-study, and practice.

Internship

Neputertech Pvt. Ltd. (2021/5 - 2021/7)

- Opportunity to learn from senior designers and selfstudy.
- An awesome period of skill development and growth

SKILLS

React JS / Next JS

Node JS / Express JS

HTML-5

Cascading Style Sheets (CSS3)

Javascript / Jquery

Figma

React Native

